TODO:

Character Generator:
	-add a character concept display and wire up method

	-In the charm UI, load only purchaseable charms
		-load MadLetter charm cascades with the help button
			-make the madletter cascades overlay the charms, not replace them
	-Health Levels
		-add to save/load also
	-Help Buttons
	-Merit Data Entry
	-Merit Layout

Possible Features:
-GM Page
-Combat Page
-Custom Charm rollers
